[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From the viewpoint of physical geography and ecology, the Ukrainian territories to the north of the Black Sea are known to contain what?", "correct_answer": "Steppes or plains", "incorrect_answers": ["Low hills and forests", "Mountains", "Sand desert"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Albuminurophobia is defined as fear of albums.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the fastest pace song in the movie tenacious D?", "correct_answer": "Car Chase City", "incorrect_answers": ["Tribute", "Papagenu", "Hes My Sassafrass"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Oxygens atomic number is 8.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Holy Roman Empire of the German Nation was a loosely coupled union of mostly German speaking principalities. Which part of the union was the driver of the 19th century unification of Germany?", "correct_answer": "Prussia", "incorrect_answers": ["Austria", "Saxony", "Bavaria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the only place in the world you can see platypuses in the wild?", "correct_answer": "Australia and Tasmania", "incorrect_answers": ["South-eastern Asia", "Hawaii Island", "South America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cameron Frye", "correct_answer": "Ferris Buellers Day Off", "incorrect_answers": ["The Great Outdoors", "Pretty in Pink", "Some Kind of Wonderful"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Much of The Longest Day was filmed in Corsica in Mediterranean Sea. There was a nudist colony just 2 miles from the beach where the movie was filmed.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The butterfly is a relative to the crab and the lobster.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do the Transformers from the self-titled movie learn English?", "correct_answer": "The World Wide Web", "incorrect_answers": ["The Dont Tell Us", "They Already New It", "A Human Taught Them"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Earth-Two DC Universe, who does Batman partner with, and eventually marry?", "correct_answer": "Catwoman, Selina Kyle", "incorrect_answers": ["Catwoman, Kathy Kane", "Alicia Frost", "Cynthia Albert"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the stars of the classic movie Casablanca.", "correct_answer": "Humphrey Bogart and Ingrid Bergman", "incorrect_answers": ["James Stewart and June Allyson", "Henry Fonda and Maureen OHara", "Humphrey Bogart and Lauren Bacall"]}]